Gooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooo
Your heat's still poison, see the air that I breathe
I don't believe in friendship anymore
Dackers in my core
Your mask still burn, the truth's underneath
I won't mistake these snakes for-
But CO2 is the only truth we've got.
thank you for being here um yeah it's getting a little bit stupider
is that how it's pronounced so you say it's stupider things are getting kind of stupider
too stupider for me almost like reasoning with these people saying the facts the truth
they just don't get it i don't know defend somebody like actually they they they say
I don't know why I give them content. Yeah, give them content. They cuck it
I mean, it's like I'm right there about to like have a fight with beat on Sandman's
So he really does care if he says I care more about money than content
He's so excited to get a clap for me every time and it's okay. I knew I was gonna make him a few bucks, you know by
Coming up. I think it's I don't know who it was
I
Mean I figured I just remembered last night, you know Christine for months has been just like
You know doxy me saying I'm you know killing babies and stuff for month and then someone reminded me
Christine's not even her real name. She said she named herself after that murdering car in the Stephen King book
right and
That car did kill a lot of people
I don't know a hundred percent if there were if the car, you know killed anybody underage
But it probably did
You know it probably did
Does anybody know if it if it?
Got anybody underage because that's what she names herself after a killer car
There's a Stephen King book called Christine if you don't know and it reminded me
Hold on who is it?
Who is it?
Hold on. I'm getting a knock on the door. I think concrete Larry
Is it paid for no, no, I didn't order it. I'm sorry. Yeah, this is it, but I didn't I didn't order it
Yeah, and how much does she like remember would be to his cry
Crying about she's getting you know doorknots and stuff like that from this guy, and then she's gonna be like I'm gonna send
You typing his first name in the chat as evidence for him like really beta
Really beta that's why they call you be tarred. I mean it really is
It's like I don't know how what your brain could get or whatever, but it can't get any wetter. I don't think
So anyway, I tune into her and guess what she's doing another spider ritual another one
It's the tiniest little spider. It's a tiny little spider. Oh
Oh my and then a time
It's not psyche wink wink. I know what wink wink means
It means there's a little secret going on behind the scenes, right?
Time, are you in on this too?
Yeah, wink, wink.
And then, I mean, first of all, I was having a dream.
I dreamed I was in this beautiful house, nice hardwood floors,
and then this woman with a huge afro of black hair and a moomoo
comes walking in with a vacuum cleaner.
And I was like, uh-oh.
And then I felt myself sucked into the vacuum cleaner and then I saw the same woman put me into a toilet and flush it and say
Bye bye psyche. It wasn't me. It was one of my
Billions of baby spiders that I have and I have a spider army. Have you seen spider awakens tarot? He's in the army
But he's a lieutenant. He can't go into the battlefield because he's too valuable, but I mean actually this spider is sad like talk about
That was a baby spider. It was she killed she actually killed a baby spider
He knew if you believe how much of a threat of baby spider is a
Baby spider have that poor? That was my baby
She killed it
She thinks it's me. No, it's just a part of my energy
But you know what the energy cannot be created destroyed it always returns back to me and I'll make more spiders
Okay, I'll keep sending them to your house
And you can keep flushing them or whatever
Just crazy guys. It's absolutely insane
By the way, this is this stream is for entertainment purposes only
Take what I have to say with a grain of salt at times other times and being totally on but
Actually, this is not scripted show. This is real. I mean, this is all real. I mean you can go watch it
Then there's somebody with my my you know, basically my family's name
And there and I'm like that's a Docs is like even Christine. She's like
Yeah, well, it's closer to my real name than it is to yours Christine you dummy. Okay. Anyway
Thank you
Come look at my bikini. Oh, no. Oh my god, I want to know if I'm ever bulimic
Okay, I don't want to say that that's like, you know, like none. Please get some help from eating disorders if you ever have that problem
That's okay, but anyway, yeah
If I ever need to if I ever need to make myself sick, I'm just gonna pull up Christine's bikini photo
Wow
I mean, it's like, and then she's just screaming at me and it's like, and then she brings KZ up.
Oh, KZ. I mean, just like, talk about how can it get any dumber than this.
Oh, and then he's like, oh, beta, he called you just texted me to come on.
She's like, show the message.
And it said, the message said, go on to betas.
So obviously, Bita didn't message that to him, unless she refers to herself.
Ever referred to herself as Bita in the first third person or whatever?
She's known to do that.
But I don't think she did that unless text message.
And I was even trying to defend Sweet Pea, blah, blah, blah.
I was like, I have the message if you want that he sent into Sweet Pea.
I have the screenshots of that, Bita, because someone sent that to me.
It was so hilarious.
And she just ignores me.
and then she's then she then I finally like leave because I'm just so disgusted by the stupidity
and she's like
Oh, she's like, oh, he got mad and quit.
I just got, I just got sick of the stupidity.
Oh, also, she's like, oh, Psyche, you know, you,
you're so, and she talks about porn bombing and stuff.
I was trying to tell her about 300 Glow.
He's going around putting a gun in his mouth
into his head on streams, trying to warn her.
She won't let me get my words out.
And then she's like, well, you're so dumb
that you got porn bombed by your own short.
And I saw it for two weeks there.
And I was like, and you didn't like say, hey Psyche,
You accidentally have like a porn bomb accidentally on your shorts.
She didn't tell me. She's like, well, that was part of your karma.
So that's how much of a friend she is, really.
I did have my channel taken down for that particular thing.
They're just like, hey, just taken down because of that.
And she didn't think in her mind to say, hey, Jamie, how are you sweetheart?
To tell me. And I did, I was on Sam Man's Defending Jamie and stuff like that.
Like leave Jamie alone because Jamie's a nice person and she didn't do anything to you
And she's not she's not like that much of a public figure
Here and you don't need to book to bully Jamie and stuff. And so I hope he gets the message about that
That's why I kept kicking him off last night because he was kind of going after her for no reason and stuff and you know
Okay, but I was trying to be funny. I was trying to go on their shows. I may say I'm in some money
I probably could have made B to some money if she would have kept me on a little longer.
Christine probably would have broken down and sent her or something, but you know, okay, whatever.
I mean, I mean, I get harassed by these people. She's actually going to send
a person named Benjamin from Wisconsin. My
In chat saying Benjamin from Wisconsin and calls that a dogs and had times be out in her chat for that
Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay
What did you miss? Yeah, it was just it was just a little bit of the normal insanity that's going on in this community
I'm as usual trying to be helpful and be a team player kind of and like hey
We're all content creators. We can all kind of like, you know laugh behind the scenes about this stuff
But it's like they're actually like just cruel people
You're gonna deliver my karma? No, no, no, no God you don't believe in God be the you've said it many times
I do believe in God and maybe a God wants to use me as an instrument for karma
God can right are just wishes you stayed on beat his panel so we could talk to you. I wish so too, but she decides to
Be a bit he can talk to me here
I mean she decides to like tell me to shut the fuck up when I'm trying to like defend her ass
Like that's why I left I was like
KZ well if beaded didn't send the text who did because he said be to send the text shut up say
He's just gonna shut your fucking mouth. Then I'm like I was like, oh
I'm just gonna try to defend you and you're gonna tell me to shut the fuck up
That's just a beauty abusive to me
Can you imagine trying to defend somebody and then they fucking do that shit to you like say that
I was trying to fucking sit there and defend her
I don't always I don't get it. I just don't get it. And then I was like, well, Bita, you know
They're doxing my family members on your show. I sent you a text. Well, I blocked you in my text
I'm like, well, how am I supposed to let you know? I'm being doxed in your chat. I mean, it's crazy. It's just crazy
It's crazy. It's crazy
Yeah, you never did Jamie you never did you've always been good
Jamie's never told me to shut the fuck up once in my entire life. Bita has done it a billion times. Okay?
Sam and sitting there calling me crack kid. I'm just trying. I'm making him money
I've probably made him more money than any of his stupid music in the past six months. Okay, but
You know
Oh
Kind of difficult in this community a little bit with such dumb tards, you know
It's like, guys, I can't even try to help them.
I can't even be actually trying to help them
and warn them about stuff without just getting shouted down.
I'm this and that.
Oh, you know what else she said?
She said, oh, fuck that Danny danger,
whatever his name was to me.
Who just died like literally two weeks ago.
She's telling me, oh, I'm crying about him and stuff.
What a bitch.
I blocked Piranha for saying something similar to that.
And then I guess Piranha's going on the rampage about me now
because I'm talking about her.
Well, Piranha, you were part of the show, you know?
You can do a season assist if you want.
But I will tell people that when I said,
oh, Danny, before he passed away, he mentioned to you
and said, where is Pai?
She's cool.
And I said, I don't know, I'm not friends with her anymore.
And then I told her that and she said,
I said, Danny mentioned to you before he passed away.
She said, ew.
That's like pretty much
What a cunt
Isn't she changing a lot? I mean it's like that that's like that's been a bit about six months
And it's like I think it was ever since like Mother's Day or like the May or around May or April or May
She just turned on me. She was mad at me because I went to Mother's Day dinner with my mom or something like that
I mean, it's like
I don't know. My dad passed away and stuff. Um, so I understand losing a parent and stuff and it was really hard and stuff
but that just didn't make any sense when she did that and I
Don't know. She's just weird. She's just like it's like a weird kind of
And then she's calling me mentally ill and he's calling me mentally ill
He sounds like like the second grades, you know
You know special those short buzz class like trying to sing those rap songs. It sounds like he's like learning how to read when he's
Singing along with a rap song. I'm not trying to like put anybody down
I'm not trying to like I'm just saying that's what comes to my mind when he's like singing along with a rap and stuff. I
Need to use the restroom. Just give me a minute guys. Okay
I'll put on just a very short little thing. Oh
I just can't take it sometimes
It's like it gets a little bit and yeah, please stay. Please stay. This is not not anything bad
It's better than Sam and his music is even better than Kodak black or I swear, but ever the shit he's putting on
I don't I mean, I mean, let me just run to the bathroom real quick. This will just take a minute. Okay
Then we'll get more into this this shit, you know
Let's fucking go
We came for the spark and the black of the night
Stayed for the truth when it bit and it fell right
Laughin' the chaos, breathin' the strange
If you felt something real, it means you changed
So keep that flame where your feet used to be
Take it with you oh
the sun don't need a throne don't need permission just a sharp little heart and a
clearing tuition if they don't get you let them stay blind we don't beg for
love we conjure our kind
Breathe in, breathe out, hold the line, seal the gate, keep the line
Okay i'm back
Let me put the link up
Anyone wants to come join me have a little chats chats go chat see after what's been happening
Just crazy. I mean at least I thank sam and for like at least like you know
I know he just put let's me up because he thinks he didn't get some cash
And I think maybe he did today. I thought someone said I was best said I guess eldo's best
But um, literally he just cucks the content because I was about to like you know have an argument with beta
And then she left and I left and so then he's back to his like like our 100 of making fun of big troll
And stuff like that. Yeah, you got to get a real life. I know I know thing that is you're fine thing that is
You're here. You're here. You're queer. I'm not not queer
Hey, by the way, that was remember we had thing that is with his brother
I remember like that bald guy showing his butt
I think that was thing that is in his brother because it looked like a you know, you think that is maybe 20 years ago
He's a great, but
Hey Mason, what's up my friend?
I was I looked closer at that picture that and it was like you did see the guy's whole button stuff
I mean that was kind of crazy
There's those are twins actually hey Kate. How are you sweetheart? Yeah, I mean if you saw what was going on like, you know
Bita not only admitted that well, she's first of all, she's letting me myself be doxxed in her chat
But then and I said well I contacted you privately. She's like well you're blocked and stuff
So how can I ever let her know about it? And then she's lying and she says she's gonna be sending the person who just sent me a pizza
He just sent her stuff to her house and sent me thousand times of concrete that she's gonna be sending him evidence against me
Okay
You dumb your worth friends Mason. We're always friends
I mean, she's so dumb and then we should have KZ on and I'm trying to defend her against KZ
His case. He's like oh beat is sent me a message telling me to be here
And she's like no I did and he read the message it said go to beat is and then he started to say that I said it
I said well, listen, it's like who sent it to you, right and
And then she said shut the fuck up to me and I just left because I was like I'm trying to defend you you dummy
And also she admitted that she saw on my channel.
I had accidentally had like one of my shorts
I didn't look at before I published it
and had a porn bomb in it
that I actually had my channel taking down over.
And she said she saw it for two weeks
and never said anything.
Cause she thought she thought that was my karma.
Okay. And she's struck in my channel before too.
So it's like, she's not my friend, right?
She's not anybody's friend, I don't think.
I think she has some serious stuff going on
with her mental state and wow.
Crazy, this is absolutely crazy though. We're still friends Mason
Okay, he's not he's kind of boring. I don't get the con I don't get it
I he's banned from my chat like I've continued to ban him. Yeah, this is the best the best content
I've made of Casey actually I found his old mom, you know his old modeling shoot
Some exclusive photos from when he used to be a model. We've seen you've seen a this is kind of behind the scenes
This was him modeling
Somebody did say he doesn't look homeless enough. I think this was before his modeling days
Or at before his homeless days when he was in his modeling
Yeah, but that's what it really looked like
Oh, I'm getting another knock on the door. Excuse me, please not the police
I didn't order anything
They're dead two times get keep locked that number. I don't I didn't order it
Yeah, it's locked that person. I think they're out of the country. They're out of the state. I think they're just rassing
Yeah, I'm sorry. They're wasting our time. They're wasting your time. I know
Yeah, no more just take my address up I'd order to grow up over door to ask you
No
Yeah, how do you call them and talk to them?
Yeah.
That was Domino's.
They're pretty concerned that they had actually two people,
because that was the second time
tonight that they've gotten an order
and they had the manager there
and they have a different number.
Yeah, so anyway.
Um, yeah, I will I mean, I should I should you know, I did get you know a few bucks last night
From somebody I guess he admitted it
You know the elbow paid to get Sam on the show for five minutes. I I think he did get five minutes of airtime and stuff
Crystal Marie that was a good show. Oh, excuse me Crystal Marie was um
Last night you like this you like the stream last night booty goon
Yeah, and it's like oh my gosh. You're you know, they're so offended and say it's a disgusting like that
I was talking about Mars blood and stuff like that. This is actual magic secrets. I'm giving away
I mean there's like, you know
Stuff with semen and and menstrual fluid people are doing I know it is kind of icky when you think about like how I
Had an ex-girlfriend that put something in my spaghetti sauce and stuff and then
You know to fall in love with there and stuff like that, but
Yeah, you miss crystal Marie crystal Marie was on for a couple hours last night
I fell asleep, but Jamie and Crystal and clumsy all kind of came to his piece. I heard
Came to like, you know, because Crystal was kind of like mad at him at first and then Jamie
I haven't watched it, but Jamie told me
that um
Yeah, yeah, and also we figured out like
Someone reminded me, you know how Christine has just been going from months and months and months about how I
Doxxed her and said that you know making up accusations and stuff. Her name is not even Christine
She named herself after the Stephen King
murdering car and
Somebody tell me if you read Christine the book is there either a minor in the book or in the
In the movie that it gets hit by that car
Yeah, Crystal Marie was funny. I mean I can I can show you like a few minutes of it
Like if you want to see like what happened last night, I kind of missed the end of it
But it was it was pretty funny
Let me bring it up. Oh, we have a little bit of last night for some re reappearance
Oh, and then be that was like oh, and you know, she said basically said F F your you know dead friend
She said Danny danger or whatever said oh who cares blah blah, you know, it's just like so cold and cruel
He just died literally his I don't think his body is the perfectly cold yet, and she's like making fun of him
And then they're like, oh, well, you're making fun of the dead. They're making fun of the dead
They're calling also Michael the piece of shit and stuff. I mean, this is sick people. There's sick people. I
never
Said horrible things like these about these people like they're like they're saying I mean they're sick
Let me get some crystal Marie from last night. It's pretty good. I see
You show I missed them a bit. So here's
You can see my hair is getting a little bit wild. I
Probably was a little bit two sheets or three sheets the wind is three sheets of the wind last night
I'll show a little bit of the crystal Marie appearance last night
Okay, here we go
Okay, so Marie
I'm gonna see some here we go guys. This is last night's crystal Marie appearance
with clumsy and Jamie fuck you over even even your boy did thank you i i don't
even know how many boy your prism i think fuck you over
Aldi right you gotta say because my boy's Aldi that's why he crystal Marie you
cannot be mad at Aldi because he didn't want nothing to do with you
Oh my gosh, she was harassing me! Haven't you seen how I...
Bruce Lee, stop!
It's the oil! It's the oil!
He still does weird shit to me!
You're a weirdo, too.
You guys are weird, dude.
Yes, I'm weird. I'm weird.
You guys need to figure out life.
before it catches up, because it's going to catch your hands up with your face and you're going to lose more than two teeth in anything because that was just a little fucking, that was just a little dare I had, okay, that was just a little dare.
I'm not a fucking kid.
Oh, you know, he's like, you're the fucking dead man.
He's like, you want the content, too, nigga?
He's a whole fucking John.
Yeah, country is a weirdo, nigga.
That ain't gonna be doxxing kids or type shit, nigga.
Yeah, do let him back up for five minutes.
Yeah, nigga, you want to tag kids.
You wrote that in the DM to Vita.
Why, nigga, don't talk about it again.
Why don't you call the cops?
Nigga, I don't need to call the cops.
You're the weirdo, nigga.
Go ahead, let's go.
Cook it up.
So Jamie what you want so Jamie so Jamie fun is the answer, right Jamie you wanted to answer
Jamie I'm talking to you. I didn't use a female come see I didn't know you a trimo
I know you, I know you, you take it up your ass, you take it up your ass, you take it up your ass, you take it up your ass, you take it up your ass, you take it up your ass, you take it up your ass, you take it up your ass, you take it up your ass, you take it up your ass, you take it up your ass, you take it up your ass, you take it up your ass, you take it up your ass, you take it up your ass, you take it up your ass, you take it up your ass, you take it up your ass, you take it up your ass, you take it up your ass, you take it up your ass, you take it up your ass, you take it up your ass, you take it up your ass, you take it up your ass, you take it up your ass, you take it up your ass, you take it up your ass, you take it up your ass, you take it up your ass, you take it up your
Yeah, what's one clumsy
For life. I hate him for life. He did he did weird shit to me before and I'm not
Ever gonna be cool with that guy. I just don't pick hang on a second. I can't get this stupid Android to shut up
I'm gonna say with iPhone. I just don't pick sides. That's you know, I get him. Yeah. Yeah, yeah
And I'm trying to be cool with clumsy
as much as I can be
and I still
Fuck any year fuck
I don't even know what I did to that and now it just makes everything you just
Drove everything back up dude, and you make me
Ew, you're so sick, and I fucking you want to fucking rip your fucking head off, dude
Like, I can't stand this fucking guy, dude.
I can't stand motherfuckers.
Damn, the chat cookin', chat to the chat.
Chat cookin', dang.
Let him back on.
That's the nastiest shit.
Facts.
They can try to play innocent.
Like, he's not nasty.
Pack yourself up, nigga.
You're the weirdo.
But so are you fucking, you're fucking, want to fucking be an owner of fucking theater.
So are you Saman? I can try to own me and shit. Mm-hmm. Oh
Try to own you now
He's trying to own
Trying to own me
Like he owns me like I'm his oh
Is that what it was okay, okay? I
Don't even know what he is what?
I don't understand what the beef is. Yeah, I can't I can't cook it up
She does many people and lot about it
Just like she showed be this ex boyfriend people do though, right?
Oh, talk about it
You don't need to talk. It's like you're Jamie or Katie. They ain't come to mind your business
Are you talking about your work Christine?
Go ahead. That's gonna get every license fucking lift
How is that?
How is that my my my what I've done how yeah, that bitch is gonna lose every license in the world
We're gonna make sure that shit. I will not bring her name up
He can ask me but I I have more respect for her than that. So oh
Wow, you're so sweet, aren't you?
I'm so sorry, I'm so sorry, I'm so sorry, I'm so sorry, I'm so sorry, I'm so sorry, I'm so sorry, I'm so sorry, I'm so sorry, I'm so sorry, I'm so sorry, I'm so sorry, I'm so sorry, I'm so sorry, I'm so sorry, I'm so sorry, I'm so sorry, I'm so sorry, I'm so sorry, I'm so sorry, I'm so sorry, I'm so sorry, I'm so sorry, I'm so sorry, I'm so sorry, I'm so sorry, I'm so sorry, I'm so sorry, I'm so sorry, I'm so sorry, I'm so sorry, I'm so sorry, I'm so sorry, I'm so sorry, I'm so sorry, I'm so sorry, I'm so sorry, I'm so sorry, I'm so sorry, I'm so sorry, I'm so sorry, I'm so sorry, I'm so sorry, I'm so sorry, I'm so
He came at me when it's not me that did it. Well that lady tried and I have it on record that she was saying that
I am the southern lady that we're trying to say I think she wanted
To say that they were gonna get me
5150 because they had a license in their area and that I made beat a mad
You know, it was crazy. Okay. Well, that's enough of that. I just want to tell you
So for the third time this lady's come to my door with the dominoes.
He's texting her just not really loud on the door.
He'll hand you the money in the tip.
The third time I'm telling her this person's just harassing me.
I don't order direct from dominoes.
This is the guy that Bita is going to be handing the evidence to and sending him.
Sending him the evidence so he can have a case against me or something for doxing.
And I just said Tony from Wisconsin or something in the chat.
to see his father's name and stuff. Interesting. Interesting.
I mean, what a dumb twat.
Wow.
And he's the one that sent her the concrete, too, and she's gonna be sending him the evidence that I'm doxing him.
And now he's sending pizzas to my house third time tonight.
Door knocks just her just harassing
You've seen that she's a straight lie. I know well, she's she's she's in contact with him personally privately
Hearing people talking outside. Yeah, it's be this people. I guess it's just be this people and then people were telling me
Oh, you know, Kate's doing this and they're just lying
They all dogs are you that I'm not I'm not that surprised, but it's like then it's like beta blocked me from her chat immediately
When I just said it's someone's first name in their state
That is people coming to my door actually the third time in the hour
Does she like that be the cried when that happened remember she was crying
She got one bag of concrete. I got like 35 of them over, you know, a week's period and stuff
They won't deliver concrete to my house anymore, by the way
but
You know they can get dominoes to and they're like they're like they're wasting our time. I know I know I know I know
Sad it is sad it's just so how dumb she is, you know, maybe that's karma for her
When she when it happened to her and she cries am I crying and she's like, oh, you're always crying
Do I ever actually cry I cried about Danny the other day and I cried about my father
These are people that died that they've been did they fucking you know, I don't know just fucking
Those are like the two times I've cried on
My show and they're always like you're crying. Do they know what crying is?
Well, I know she does but you know
Let's say I'm in like his father mentions. I don't know
Crazy crazy guys
So it's just like the stupidity kind of like
Hurts me. It's just like it's like stupidity hurts me. I
Think I'm out of the three. I'm pretty much like the Albert Einstein of
You go above the other two
You know
Pretty much Albert Einstein compared to like Forrest Gump and fucking
Who's another who's the guy that's like a you know Helen Keller or something like that?
No shade to Helen Keller or Forrest Gump and stuff
Beat is kind of like Helen Keller
Helen Keller was smart actually she was just you know, she was just blind and deaf and stuff
Forrest Gump was just lucky, but he was
Definitely on the lower side of the spectrum and stuff, but not no shades of forest gump and whatever no shared divorce gump or Helen Keller
I mean and then she's like oh and then she like she's like you know
The spider stuff is like kind of like a kind of like it just like kind of a funny joke
I think kind of just like
You know me trying to be like funny about stuff
Oh, you're kissing me between spider. She actually she gets offended. She's actually offended. I'm like, are you
Yeah, and then Christine keeps putting the sui is the IDE number
It's sort of Bathory. They're like 988 988
Like stop, you know, stop putting that in the chat. I mean, it's like unless somebody really needs that number
I don't need that number. I was saying that there's some coercers in the community
And maybe that did it. Do I feel like the picked person in self-projecting ironic's picture is attractive? Let me have a look
Self-projecting ironic. I don't I don't see that person. I think I might have them blocked. Oh, here. I see it. I see it
That person attractive. Let me see. Let me see. Who's this picture?
Is that bozo the clown?
No, I don't find them very attractive
His wife beaters a little bit too dirty. Yeah, I think it's bozo the clown. Yeah, no not my type
That's bozo the clown, right I recognize that the hairstyle
Is it bozo is that you I'm sorry, you're not you're just not my type you're not my type
Is that like is that like chicken wing stains on your wife beater
Chicken wings, you know wife beater is not a napkin and
I'm my friend Danny stranger. I was like he was I was like can I can you send me your your wife beater?
He's like he's like sure I'll send you my white beater. I
Say it's called a wife beater. He's like what?
He's wearing a pomprom. Oh, there's a prom dress
But Danny thought it was white beater.
I thought that was really cute because he wears one
and he looks really good in one, right?
But he thought it was called a white beater.
Up into, you know, it's like,
so before he passed away,
I got to tell him the correct word for white beater
and I got to, you know, send a lot of people to his chat.
And so those are a couple of good things, you know?
But he was surprised.
He's like, I thought it was,
he's like, I always thought it was white beaters.
It's just kind of adorable to me. It's just kind of adorable. He was a adorable person, you know
And how dare you beta for putting his name in my mouth and making fun of him and stuff
It's but this person was just murdered
And you think it's funny
Or something to make fun of me about like what's your problem?
You're sick you are sick
Yeah, and then Sam and
Oh, here's our 500 of Big Trollah talking to the camera.
I mean, it's like, Big Trollah,
I've nothing against Big Trollah.
I don't really know her.
I guess people hate her or something,
but it's just her kind of looking like Daria
or something like that talking to the camera.
And it's not even anything interesting or funny
or anything, it's just boring.
Today, it was six hours of that.
I go I fast forward. Where's where's the part where I come in?
I mean he played like the little clip where I'm talking my menstrual blood and stuff, but then it's like
The rest of that was just big troll. Uh, like talking to the camera and it's like
Wait, I what is that?
Is it is she that I
And I have nothing against I just I just don't know her. I don't I haven't watched her show or anything
but
People want to watch that instead. I do have 25 people in the chat
Maybe I do have a quarter of their viewers or whatever. They may be botting. They may be who knows and whatever
It's not entertaining
It's not I was like well play is entertaining. He had beta and me up there ready to like
Mud wrestle basically and then he wants to clap that and then he's so excited to get to this big troll
I think he got some donations from somebody that just hates big troll or something like that and so
He just continues to play hours and hours. Is he getting paid must be getting paid to just do hours and hours of
Buddhist harasser of a rune show. I mean big troll. You know, you can you can strike him for that if you want
He's just playing your show
It is so it is so me unless I'm on there when I'm on there
People get hyped that the chats are starts arguing. It's like everybody gets kind of like into it
And then it's like fuck what he gets so excited when I get clapped because he gets you know like 20 bucks or whatever
He's so excited
I mean really guys
And making up yeah, she's sitting there doing her like hair and makeup like not really talking about anything
She's just sitting there doing her hair and makeup. Maybe like complaining about life and stuff and
It's like hours of like literally hours of it elders like oh fuck. I'm out of here
Like I mean he has an elder on the show at least I mean elders entertaining a little bit, right?
I'm entertaining when I'm up there. That's why he still always has me up
Even though I kicked him off like 20 times last night. He has me up and doesn't clap me and stuff. He does I know
He you know, he doesn't he doesn't give me a dime. He doesn't get it not once
He's made a couple hundred bucks probably of getting just beginning me clapped. That's why he wants me on the panel
But you know what I probably I don't know why I do I just like kind of like to hang with the
Crew or whatever like some of the people I like some I don't you know. Yeah, it's just boring
She's sitting there literally sitting at her makeup table
Putting on her lipstick for a couple hours and that's what we're what he didn't really comment on it
He's sitting there playing her show.
I'm like, what's this?
I mean, they're not really entertaining or anything.
First of all, he plays, you wait, you go there.
Oh, okay, he plays about two hours or three hours
of his donated songs.
Okay, so I'll go back three hours later,
and then, oh, then it wraps up, right?
And her of all it's because people hate her like some people like really hate her and I guess he's gotten
Attention or something or donations for that probably that's the only reason I can figure out that he would keep
Because it was like he already did her six hours this morning
I mean even play the period blood rant that I did it was for entertainment purposes only and stuff. I
Don't want to making money off me
Maybe he maybe he really needs it or something. You know, maybe I don't want to see Sam and
Homeless, I mean, I do have a heart for people. I even feel bad for KZ a little bit like having to take a bath at McDonald's everyday. I
Feel bad. I feel I do feel bad. I mean, I have a heart for people. I
Don't want to say I'm not taking a bath at McDonald's. I don't I don't that would be I don't want the mighty mighty to fall
Kind of like that, you know, they don't care if the fuck happens to me. They actually don't care if I
Die, I mean really they don't
But I do have a heart and I'm not like that to other people. I never wished I mean I've said people die
And the person that he was doxxing me outside. I said I'd die and I mean it and stuff, but it's like really
They did a new serve up people living in the sewers and I think that was that LA there's LA sewer people
I saw the I saw the Las Vegas sewer people. That's pretty interesting. There's a whole like little
City under Las Vegas actually where they have they're called the mole the mole people and they just live in the sewers in Las Vegas
Can you imagine living in the sewer though?
But what's in the sewers shit and garbage and
Like remember imagine that garbage water. I feel bad. I just like my heart is hurting just thinking about that people are living in sewers
That's sad
at least like
There's forests. I mean go like
Fucking sit
If I ever went homeless, I would basically do this.
I would just take my, all I would do is I'd take a backpack
and put my tarot decks, I'd put like five tarot decks
in there.
I would sit and say, tarot readings, $5.
And I would just do, and I would go on government
assistance and stuff.
I would eventually work my way out of it.
Even if I have any trade at all terror readings a good trade, you know, you can do that people are people are drunk coming out of restaurants and stuff
Oh, here's it's like interesting. I don't know. It's like something it's like I have a I have a trade. I have a talent, right?
It is expensive in LA, but they also have beautiful forest. Yeah, so but if I couldn't get a place I would just
Because they do give you vouchers for places as long as you stay off drugs and stuff they give you vouchers for hotels
You can stay in like actually pretty nice hotels for months at a time for free in California
now, but if anything I would do I
would get a tent and go to the forest and then I would like hunt squirrels or something like that, and I would just eat squirrels
Is that better than living in the sewer?
A little bit better just a little bit. I
Mean I'd rather just do that or just get my McDonald's
I get the ebt card for like a thousand dollars to give you like a thousand bucks or something
That'd be enough to like basically get McDonald's every day plus more, you know, I
Don't know unless they want to live in the sewers
They don't have to but I've seen how LA I've hung out with homeless people in LA
I see how it works. They have a little network of like their people
Yeah, I BL just lives in the yeah, I think there's a guy named. It's his name isn't it somebody
We got the guy's name God. He's on his channel all the time
He just lives in his car like in Florida in like the forest basically and
Then like it's donations until he can fix his car and stuff and then drives to another forest and stuff
And just looks kind of like right on the outskirts of the city
We can go into the city a little bit and stuff. We got the guy's name. I'm gonna remind me of this guy
God, he knows who he is
I
Think that's living in the woods is the woods are beautiful, right? You're in nature
It's like the sewers are just too
Gross you're literally oh here's a river of shit and piss and garbage going by my bed
Not putting anyone down.
Just saying there's better options
unless they must once live in the sewers.
Plus people jump, imagine you wake up
and a body falls on you.
The mafia throws bodies in the sewers.
That someone told me they just open a manhole cover,
throw the body in there, and then they close it.
I mean, that's how most bodies are disposed of
in Los Angeles and stuff.
Imagine a body falling on you.
I mean, it's hard enough for me to vacuum, let alone have a pile of bodies rotting in
the corner and stuff.
A lady popped out of the manhole cover, you know what I call her, I call her survivor.
Yeah, you just see this woman
First of all those banhole covers are heavy. So she has her camera on she uses one ham
Yeah, little tweakers have this they have Superman strength, you know, she has this she pushes a manhole cover up and
comes out
Scurries the scurries like a little mouse to the
Alley or something like that gives gives someone a blow job probably KZ
Okay, I'm gonna text my text somebody. I'm gonna see if I can get some weed or something
You just give it there's my phone it's around here somewhere. Oh my phone
Again guys entertainment purposes only guys
Downed it
the cat woman is letting other people Doc's names. Oh, for her first common name. And oh, the cat,
yeah, I know Clemsi. She was Doc's name, my last name, or she was letting somebody do that. Then
she was like, she was going to send him evidence. And then he's the one sending her concrete and
me concrete. I told her before. She's like, I know, I know he's doing it. Oh, look at the, oh,
Daddy
Watch that again
Daddy come to papa
Fuck I love Instagram
Look at that shit. Oh damn
One more time. Oh fuck
That is hot
Can I can I marry him
Mess I'm going to right now. Is he a friend I'm gonna say marry me
And say marry me Papa's
Okay, I said I said marry me Papa's
I did say it. Do you believe me?
Imagine me being that wall
Oh, that's what a way oh
I'm I'm I'm dead like basically
That happens and then I get shot in the head. That's my
That's my life. I'd be I would die with a smile on my face. I really would
Yeah
Whoo
Sorry, I'm eating a little bit little bit like hot guys. I'm sorry. Oh
My gosh
That's like it's like a human jalapeno a human habanero or I oh my gosh
That was fucking delicious
Do you see that? He was like, you know, he had a nice, I mean, bigger than, nicer than mine,
and he just rips off that way. Oh, that was good. Oh, I feel like I just took a shower.
I mean, I feel like I just took a warm, warm shower or something. That was refreshing.
Spicy, that was spicy
That's hot fuck let me see I'm looking for somebody's number hold on
What am I, what am I sweating?
Oh, no, honestly guys, I have like the freaking hottest
Instagram, I'm gonna see my Instagram,
I'll go through Instagram for like two minutes.
You're gonna be like, whoa, how are you not just
constantly jizzing 24 seven to me?
I'm not, oh, there's thing that is again.
And his brother, that's a young thing that is.
That's not you
That's you. That's not you. That's I'm in the couch right there. That's you. I see you. I recognize you
Are you saying stop?
Get to the chopper get to the chopper Mason you to the chopper
Hey Mason get to the chopper with me
Let's go in the helicopter
Helicopter, what is this guy doing?
Wow
I wish I was that couch
Fuck I wish I was that couch
Damn everyone so go on Instagram and trust me. I
Love schwarzenegger. This is what Sam and wishes only I can't show that one
Yum
Fuck oh
I'm truly I'm so much. I'm drooling so hard. I can't stop Kate Kate. Are you watching look at this Kate?
Yes, Jamie, I love I'm sorry. I love your foot. Look at these guys. What are these guys doing?
Oh, oh my god
What are they smelling
Okay, yeah, just rewind a little bit. Okay, look at these guys look at these guys
I'm burning like a cat
Kate can see Kate Kate Kate can see I think Kate might like this came I like it. It's not anything bad
Kate might like it
Yeah, I can see Kate and I going to the Chippendales and
Put in some hundred dollar bills and some guys
Oh, we have good times on the show good time. Okay guys
I wasn't being gay.
Gaten doesn't like that shit.
I want to keep him around for a little bit.
I wasn't being gay.
What happened to everybody else?
I saw Crystal was on here.
That was last night.
I was replaying Crystal for a little bit.
But don't leave.
Yeah, she was on last night.
It's fine.
We can talk about it.
How are you doing, dude?
I'm doing fantastic. Hey, your beard is looking good. I'm not trying to hit on you. I'm just saying it looks fucking. That's the nice beer you got.
No, it's not. Well, I can't grow facial hair. I mean, it doesn't go, it doesn't go all the way up here by my head.
You look like a young Santa Claus. I love it. Hey, good time. If you don't mind, can you just give a shout out your channel name?
Because people in chat are asking for your new, your new channel. Chicken and cakes wants it.
You don't mind it's capital letters. It's a GT space not underscore
The number four and L. Okay. There you go. I'm taking cakes. Yeah, he's streaming. He's actually like
I've been on his panel. I'm live right now. You're live right now. Hey everybody. How are you doing?
Shout outs. Well, so my my chat told me that they're bored and to join somebody stream to have a conversation
We're good. I like I like our conspiracy conversations. Oh, excuse me
I like we talk about we talked about Charles. We're in about a burp all the time. Yeah, I like the Charles Manson conversation
You got the good times shirt you have merch
Do you have merch or is that from the good times show from the 70s? Johnny Cage sent this to me Johnny Cage shout out Johnny Cage for doing that
Custom made it because I knew it was custom-made I could tell but that's really cool Johnny Cage. Hey
A custom cult of psyche shirt, maybe no, I'm just kidding. No. Wow. You can make your own merch
I know I do have my own I have a little nor I but I'll have his little Lenore sweatshirt and a lot of people click on it
But no one's bought it yet, but that Lenore sweatshirt. That's that's fire. I need to buy it too. I need to buy it too. I mean
I'll have my cat inside and she's trying to fuck with me. Yeah. Oh your cat over there
Yeah, we have a little right here. She's trying to figure out how to destroy my focus. She's jacked my elbow. Oh
Good times cat at the tashing
She's fine, but she eventually she'll jump on the keyboard or do something weird
I've had I've had my cat Larry type fucking messages on my keyboard before
My cat too and she they sometimes they almost type their name like I think tricks put a TR and then X
X X like all like all these X's and stuff and it was like he's spelling his like he's literally
He just walked over the keyboard, but it was a TRX. It was like wow that is crazy the Colts of Benny
Yeah, the Colts of Benny Blanco
That's a lot smarter than what people think I think so too. I think so even even if it's like, you know coincidence
There are no coincidences.
Sorry, I was talking to my cat.
So Lala, hey, so Lala was in the chat.
And there she is.
Hey, Lauren, like Lala, we have a mutual friend.
I'm not gonna say her name.
I'll just say her name starts with a J
and it's somebody from the Elisa Giordano universe
and stuff, but you know, she's let me know about,
you know, how Sig was sexually harassing you and stuff.
Don't, don't unsig balls.
Sig is sexually harassing you.
You know Lala, good times.
I talk to a lot of like every day on my okay. So well, it's other friends. Okay. Well, I gotta take care of my cat
My cat's trying to figure out. Okay. Go ahead. Go ahead. Go ahead. Get ready. Knock down my camera and do all kinds of weird shit
Just imagine me and Jenny. I told yeah, imagine me. I'm not gonna leave
But I got a trick. I got a tricker in the kitty prison. All right. Yeah, don't call Jamie words
I'm imagine me and Jenny because I unbanned you itself, but don't call people the R word again. Okay
just don't do it. Jamie is one of my lieutenants. And so, you know, she wants to ban you. She can.
She doesn't. She doesn't. But she doesn't. She didn't. I think I banned you for calling me that.
But don't, don't, like, Jamie's nice. Like, and I'm sorry if people can confuse my behavior
for Jamie's and stuff, because Jamie really doesn't ban. Like, she's more of, like, the,
the chat, like, she's like, she's, first of all, she's a huge heart. Second of all, she's always
She says hi to everybody and knows everybody and she likes everybody except unless you're Mason. Are you me? She doesn't quite
Like them very much. Yeah, I got her. Well, I
When I say kitty prison, I just have her leg in the other half of the house and
She can't jump on my computer. Yeah, Jenny. I
call it kitty
And why I put up with Jenny a little bit even though Jenny called me names Jenny did donate five memberships
I do appreciate people and Danny also was is a member. I'm not sure if they're still a member
They might have expired their membership, but no they expired, but
She hates you. I don't think Jamie doesn't really have hate in her heart for anybody unless you're Mason or
You me I don't think she
Likes them very much. I don't think it maybe even hates them, but she strongly dislikes those guys
because they're
We are we are on team Jamie like forget me. Yeah, Jamie
Question do you drink a lot of coffee or do you take at all do I?
Yes, I today I've all I've all I've done is I have another iced coffee
I had two iced coffees from McDonald's and I slept all day
So what I have energy plus I've been drinking a couple drinks, but
Hey, they're not doing that
I was just asking you on this question
I know who has that flip flop asset in the chat or something flip something
Well, you're you have a very hyperactive person. I know I think I might be bipolar and my it was flip right as they might be
But I've never seen you calm in my entire life. Look at there's flip flat in my chat, too
Well foot flat watches me. Yeah, I know I saw them in your chat today
They asked me the same question. They're like are you like on meth or rid or riddolin or Adderall or something
I was like, I'm just maybe bipolar. Well, they replace riddolin with Adderall. Yeah
I mean riddolin is like like Adderall is actually like
amphetamine pill. Ritalin is like a little bit different and stuff, but yeah, I saw you.
I saw you.
Ritalin will make you tweak out, too.
Yeah, yeah.
When I was-
Picking up a bit. I need to take like 20 of them to do that.
No, no, no, no, not even that. I had a friend in high school that was on Ritalin. He was
a fucking weird guy. But once in a while, I'd ask him for a couple of Ritalin pills.
I'd get home from school and fucking, I'd grind them up and snort them and I'd just
Pacing around my parents basement fucking sweating shirtless like
Like fucking tweaking off
Yeah, she's not you know, you know, I guess that means I don't have attention
That's it. I do too because I have actually when they like I was actually I had a
Adderall prescription during the pandemic because you could just do like over the over the
the internet, doctor visits and get a prescription.
And so for several months, I was able to just,
but then I would get like a prescription of like 30 pills
and I would have finished it in like three days.
You sure I didn't say too much about it.
I won't say too much about it.
I'm gonna shut up.
But then they stopped that program.
So I'm actually been very sober for, since the pandemic.
So I don't know, but I do think I have ADHD
or bipolar or something like that,
but I don't like taking medications really.
I don't I don't either I I'm prescribed gab patent and clomping. I don't like taking it every day
Like but I'm just imagining you like, you know
Okay, never mind. You're you're you're taking a lot of riddle in your basement and doing back and forth doing doing like
Wait lifting weights or something
All he knows is that Shay got me tweaked the fuck out.
Yeah, he does, he does.
I want to rate him.
I had a friend that actually needed it.
He's very smart and he's rich now.
he, um, he was, he was to describe Rylan when he would take it, he would act perfectly normal.
But if he wasn't on it, his mind was all over the place.
Right, exactly. Well, some people, like, because it's like, it does calm, like, the nerves.
If you have ADHD, it will kind of, like, calm your nerves and stuff.
And if you don't, they will just get you twacked out and stuff.
But, um, you know, everyone has, like, a different...
Yeah, you're mistaken Janie and just just be polite to uh to Jamie. Yeah, I don't think Jamie's did anything to you ever
So just and you're unbanned and so just like, you know, I hope you unless you unless you actually like
Disputed the charge of buying the memberships you're gonna stay unbanned, okay
But if you actually like the speed of the charge that folks with
my YouTube yourself then
Was your chat fighting with you? I can't see your child. No, let's imagine being a Janney was it's kind of like fighting with Jamie a little bit
But I think the down they said it's a mistaken identity thing, so
You know Jamie good times
No, I don't
Sounds like she doesn't like you
Me Jamie's Cowboys is my mod for
Just said they're there
No, no, Janney not Jamie imagine being a Janney not Jamie
No, yeah, what you got per Nazi word slowly, okay? I'm sorry
Hey, you know Alexander struck my channel again
for what?
For doing a short with like 30 seconds of her stupid show talking about me
Um, yeah, she struck that so well, she she gave me copy your straight copy your a strike one time
So she was on outcast owls, and I don't even want to talk about what she's talked about, but I edited it. I
Edited it and I I put up live
She owned the copyright to it because it wasn't her show, right?
She put this copyright strike for my picture with her at dinner good times
My picture. All right. We'll stop talking about her ignore. Okay. I'll ignore. I'll ignore. I'll ignore. She's a ignore it
Don't even talk about her
She did this just dream about how oh
I'm just really imitating her in chats now because there were so many with her name in the chat
So she is he's petty. She's very petty exactly Vinny wants to be a host on your channel. Let him let him
But can I be a host to Janie?
Can I take over your panel one day, please? I'll be good. I promise you have me and Benny
And then we can talk all about whatever you want to accuse us of like, you know, I didn't groom Benny
He grew me
Benny and Joker grew me
Okay, they're both 25 years old, okay, but they grew me they grew me to be a YouTube streamer
Let me tell you something Joker is a troll. He trolls everybody. Yeah
Hold on I'm getting a I'm getting a message. Let me just I'll get back home. Okay
Okay
Yeah, okay. I don't know what that what that was. I think maybe at least oh, it's in my chat. Let me see what's going on
on my cults of psyche
Trip and sip is promoting something called the Thorpe tube. I
Don't know what they just got a message for is it Lisa at your daughter. I don't know
Kermit and friends is very active. Hey, and I was by the way, at least and I are still you know
We still get along. I just haven't been to her chat that much or if I matter chat
I don't really talk in her chat because I have
you know some evil trolls or I don't want to like bother anybody else because of me and stuff
where are the cats well tricks is right here and Rudy's right here and Lois right there
seriously I've been around mathematics you seem like you're on math I'm not I'm not anything I'm just
on coffee do you know do you know how to calm down
Take a deep breath and meditate and stuff.
Yeah, I do that when I go to sleep and stuff,
but right now, I like to be kind of,
like a little bit of a little amped for my show,
just so I have energy and stuff on my show.
But I'm not on the drug.
I'm not, I'm just basically, except for caffeine.
This is my first McDonald's coffee,
and I have a whole other one,
and I started drinking too.
So I'm a little bit,
Alcohol gets me a little bit amped, but you know I'm drinking I almost finished it
I finished this whole whole drink to smash
And I got another one so I you know people on meds really don't drink, you know
Actually they do
They do. Well, and then that's my horror limit. Yeah, this might be a mannequin. You know what the hell's angels would do?
They'd stay up all night drinking and the morning they'd smoke mat to wake up and they they'd fucking ride their motorcycles
Well, that sounds dangerous
well
You know, it's dangerous as being high on math
Well, I'm not I'm not so sure you sure. Yeah. Show me your pupils
Okay, they're not they're not pinned. They're not no
I'm not if I swear I
swear to God
No, Matt, I swear swear to God
Maybe I should try it. Maybe no don't
Math, you're already hyperactive enough. Maybe it'll calm me down if I have ADHD
No, well, it'll make you run around naked in the middle of the street
Based on your person. I've only done that. I've only done it a few times. Hey, I'm speaking of
So you've done that. No, but not on that but just you know, just for fun. I'll do it right now
This is your stream it is do do whatever you want. I don't care
I'm gonna do a muscle. I'm gonna do a flex show. You need to get a weight set. I mean my arm. I have a pull-up bar
You look like you're dying from HIV
What if I really was would you feel stupid saying something so horrible?
if you actually did die from HIV, AIDS,
I have to rear after.
I don't, because you know what, I'm very disease-phobic.
And so I really have any, I'm practically a virgin.
I'm practically a virgin.
I'm also a top, and so it's kind of rare.
It's not very nice, good time, but it's okay, it's okay.
We're just, you know what, it's kind of like bros.
No, no, I'm like, listen, I have,
you know, medical issues, like I don't have sexually transmitted diseases, but like I was just curious
This just next time say Auschwitz or something like that. You look like you need to put a little weight
Hey, I mean eating a Big Mac a fries and two coffees a day at least
That enough food I
Don't know you just look like you're not doing good
Hey, I mean I can show you my body. Hey. Hey. Hold on. This is from somebody you're I want to see your body. Go ahead
Well
Shape of shit because I've been in my house on winter. It's okay. We're gonna have as a good times good times show. Here we go
Here I'll do it, too
Okay guys, what do you think?
Good times is a little bit better. Yeah, he looks a little bit better. I
Like it I like it. I'm gonna put my shirt back on too
I'm gonna put it on. Oh, you know, you can keep yours off. I like it. Well, yeah, it is a party now now. It's a party
Beaches that way yeah, I'm putting it back on too thing that it okay thing that is got scared away
Thing that is left thing that is we're just comparing our bodies. What it's a human body
Why is thing that is such a little oh, oh, I mean, I'm gonna leave yeah, that's a tricksy one thing that is come on
Our shirts are back on
But you came I don't even want to imagine what you're just saying you're saying
Good times it says why are good times arms so thin?
It's a body off it's a tricks and then there's a bunch of laughing emojis
Awesome, I love it. It was not too bad. I think it's I think we got off pretty easy for that one
Well, what's I start mowing the grass?
My arms are gonna get some work. What is the times channel again? It's gt
dash
Space gt space for number
Number four
Capital capital L
We can't see who has the biggest dong booty band it because that would be against TOS, but
I've never flashed my penis on anybody. I'll say I'm eight inches. What are you can say you can if you ever measured yours
Yeah, he's around fully to it's about eight and three quarters. Yeah. Oh, he might be bigger. He's almost nine inches. Damn
Good times any time you need a friend good time. Oh, there you go careful. Okay perfect
I love it perfect. Yeah, so good times is like wow good times has the biggest cock in the panel verse
I think I'm second place
There I've been said dick pics by people for mr. Big Pipes. It was
Me too. I know he was jerking off. He wouldn't send me him jerking off
He just sent me with him in underwear with his with his wiener hard a couple of those pictures. Yeah
Well, why does he did why does he send those to us?
I think to do that to another man, you're probably gay.
I think so too.
I think Mr. Big Pipes.
He might be gay, possibly.
You just might be, because I haven't,
I mean, there was this guy in Meezer,
and I did, you know, a little naked show for Meezer before
because he's gay and stuff,
but that's the closest I've got.
But say I'm mad because you wanted KK Link,
but he porn bombed, right?
He wanted KK's Link, but then he showed us his vagina, right?
I'll always refer to the six vagina from now on
You're 300 you're 300 loaded on my stream last night twice
I can get well, you know, I don't know if you know this but saying in 300 glow they talk on discord
And yeah, they're boyfriend. I mean their boyfriend. They look literally they try to figure out how to fuck up somebody's live stream
Yeah, well 300 glow and he first he showed his wife and his wife is a really sweet lady
I think her name is Dean or something like that. Well, don't talk about names, but
Okay, I'm sorry, but he was saying it last night on the show and stuff
He's like, here's my wife and she was on camera for the first time
I've never seen her on camera. She's making a nice inch a lot of plate and I so I let him up because I
Like her and that's why I let him up because she was on camera and stuff and I've never seen her on camera and then I
Turned my head for a second. I look back. He's pointing a Glock at the chat
Then put it in his mouth and put it to his head and stuff
it was it was it was it a 9mm or was it a 38 because I've seen him do it with a 38.
I think he must just have the 38.
Was it a revolver?
It looked like it was just a black gun.
It was like a black, it was a big kind of chunky black gun.
Oh no, I got a 9mm laying right next to me.
I got 38 in my bedroom, whatever.
all legally bought
please don't show it
F.B.I. backer attracts all these show shit
I mean you have on my show before
but I think you really kind of didn't like me as much
I think we've kind of like come to like
we're kind of like bros now
So you wouldn't do that, right? Well, well you respect me. I respect people
I will and I've got if I ever come on your show and done anything like that. I would I would I was always
You've never done anything weird on my show. Yeah, I try to be cool and then Christine comes on and then
And then
You heard it comes on and it's like
Too many people against me four people against ones
I didn't know what you do to piss them off. I know they don't like me
But I don't know but I mean, but it's like
I'm too real. I like I like how your numbers went up though
I like your numbers were like they're going up and stuff like that and I'm sorry
I like leave cuz I just get too overwhelmed. It's hard to like
It's this voice, it's this voice, it's this voice, it's this voice, it's this voice, yeah.
All those voices, it's like too confusing and I get overwhelmed and I leave and then they
all leave and then it's like, but I'm happy your numbers.
Go up, you know, I don't I don't care about I know you don't I know you're not
Yeah, I don't treat stream is a popularity
I know it's not but it's like I still it's still it's a good feeling when you have a lot like you know
My friend Danny he just passed away and stuff or he had murdered actually, but he he had he had a video though
And viral so he had one that video it said I got fired from Walmart
It had 1.2 million views on it and he had like 23,000 subscribers or something
But he always had two or three people in his chat like, you know
Usually women that kind of had a crush on him or me that had a crush on him
And I sent my chat over there
He had 40 people and he was like just a big smile on his face and like so happy and
He said I had the best time. He had the best time
Joker's a complete jackass
So I was live-streaming I thought my cow was dead because I knew it was getting ready to die
Hey, um, not this cat, my old cat, but um, I was, I was crying about it because I was sad and um Joker
Clipped it and put it on tiktok. He got 2.3 million views as mostly
Chinese people laughing about how they would have ate their cat. I know Chinese people are sick
You know what? I mean that is pretty sick and it's like it was just like that horrible sweet pee woman
You know, she's like 500 pounds and never cams up or anything and then she has a channel
It's all me on her channel and it gets more views than I do on my show
Like her channel just making fun of me, you know, so
You know, what can you do? What can we do? You know, we just have to like fucking. Hey, maybe hopefully though
She could at least I put my channel
Or my name on it, you know, she could at least like just like Sam and it's like
Say man, how about like a shout out to my channel because you're using literally all of my content
It'll restrain this stream tomorrow
I know well no because he's been just doing big trolla for the past like six weeks
Like it's just big troll doing her makeup basically in six hours of that and then maybe like
And one of sweet piece clips of me and that's like the highlight of the show and then it's just big troll
doing her makeup and shit right and it's like
Like why are you doing this and I don't I don't understand. I should have I should have I should have
300 people I can understand
I should have like so many more people.
But you know what, 30 people, well,
Bita is live, I'm sorry, I'm saying Bita's live
and Sam and his live right now,
30 people is not fucking bad because once,
if they were both not live right now,
I would have 100.
I'm not even looking to see how many people are watching me.
You know, so you know, Bita said to me today,
she's like, well, she's like,
I saw you poor mom yourself.
and I saw for two weeks you had it on your shorts. You had an accidental porn bomb. I had my actual channel taken down here.
You should not care.
I have no no but this poor mom I actually got my channel taken down for that porn bomb and then I got it
I got it brought back by a miracle, but
I was like, well, why didn't you tell me and she's like, well, that's your karma
Why why do you why do you want to talk about people that don't like you?
We were friends at one time good times. Yeah, it doesn't matter
She's your friends. You say you say you're not her friend. She's on your show. She's on your show
barely ever you're on her show every time you always come up there. Why are you mad at me?
She kicks me almost immediately because you said you say that Edward with the heart are
The Sam and well Sam and calls. He says I know it's a double standard
It isn't sick and he's not even black. You know Sam is not black. I know. I know
It's so crazy. I
Mean I could join the stream right now. Can I take the time you want to go join a stream right now?
Not say a man. Okay. We can both do it and that he'd be really confused
No, he would just kick me booty bandit, I'll tell you the story
Alexander wanted his semen to have a child
And then he's like, okay
I won't talk to the child until the child is three years old because that's when they learn to talk and then she turned against them
That's the story. Well, it's like no, it's a story. That's actually true. That's true
the
You can actually talk to them to talk to me can't you just like rub some come off of her belly from left over from her porn days and get pregnant
I don't understand. All right. That's sweet. Okay. That's too much. That was that was I would do
Hey, you she struck my channel good times. So I I
She fucking fucks with everybody. Yeah, she fucked with me. So I'm sorry. No, no, that's the true story
Me and her we're talking on discord back in the day
And she's talking about how she wanted to have a kid.
And I said, well, you want to have a kid,
I can get you pregnant.
And then she said yes, right?
Well, yeah, she was down for it.
And then I said, I don't want to talk to a child
till he's three years old, so I can actually talk to it.
And she's like, what?
You don't want to be the father and raise the kid?
And I'm like well, of course not. I mean it's like she said sperm donor
She didn't say I want you to get me. She get married and stuff, right?
Well, I think that's why she's thinking well. Oh my god women sometimes right women sometimes
That's why I like because I just had a bad feeling
I was like I feel like she was attracted to me and stuff like that
I feel like something could have happened that night if if like she but then I was like I
Well, I'm not gonna cross any lines. I'll be accused of a great being or something like that, right?
So I was always, I did, I actually met her in person.
She came out, picked me up, took me to dinner, paid for the whole thing.
We smoked a joint outside if there's IRL we did and stuff.
Shit. It was fun. It was, it was all good. It was all good.
Everything was chill. You know what she says now?
Now she says, I'm so ugly.
So, so women will notice stay away from me.
She said, I smell.
I was covered in cat hair, even though she had me the next day in her car
for like three hours when we drove to Hollywood and stuff.
If you said I was so dirty and smelly,
would you want me in your car for three hours, really?
But whatever, whatever.
And plus, she is accused of getting kicked out
of the porn industry for having a smelly.
I am not going there.
Okay, okay, okay, I'm gonna shut up.
But that's true.
I mean, that's true though.
But okay, I'm gonna shut up.
I'm gonna shut up.
I didn't think that's the next subject next subject next subject and so hey can someone join the panel where I'm here with good times
And we're you know what we're having we're having some good times tonight. I think I'm drinking a little bit
I'm drinking a little bit, too. I'm then my second heart eliminated
okay
Hey
Go to beat is here. You're here. Oh
Thank you, sir. This is that go to Sam is oh
Thank you. This isn't that
It was one free troller
What am I chat you're gonna see good times, and I just laughing like bros
Yeah, I chill out. That's all I do. I do too. I do too. I
Mean, oh, we have a guess. Let's welcome black RG. Oh, oh, hold on. I'm gone. Okay. Okay. Bye. Good times
I'll see you later. Okay. Come back. Let's talk to him. No, I have a good one. I
Just I just want to see him run like a little bitch. That's all I don't even have anything to say
He's just such a little bitch made fun of him and what do you make fun of you made fun of something about him?
He was getting on page right bleatley hitting on page. I was making fun of him
So now he's trying to do what Lala does and and just run
But since he's a dude it doesn't work it makes him look like a huge bitch, which is funny. It's funny to me, right?
And RG, you know, I don't have a problem with you.
Hey, RG, but what do you think about what happened at Beat Us today?
Because I saw the last 20 seconds of it.
Well, here's what happened.
First, I just turned on to Beat Us channel.
She's having another spider ritual.
Oh, another spider.
Hold on.
Yeah.
The spider ritual was her killing a spider because there was a spider.
Did she say that?
No, the first time she actually named the spider Psyche.
And then she said this.
She said this.
I read the transcript.
She said this is a secret spider ritual.
Psyche better watch out.
She flushed it.
Then tonight there was a bit.
It was like the tiniest little baby.
It was like a tiny little.
The tiny little black on her white wall or whatever she gets a vacuum that I was having actually a dream
I saw a woman with a huge black afro and a moomoo
Vacuuming me off the wall and flushed me down the toilet and I said what's going on
I woke up and I turn on beat is and you're the spider in this I get it
I'm the spider. I'm the spider and then she's like well what what and then okay then
You know this person, I don't know if you know this person, but I said Tony from Wisconsin
Okay, and then she's like you're doxxing. I'm gonna report you to him
I'm gonna screenshot and send this to him. He sent her the concrete to and he sent me three
I just want to point out that you let me up so fast because you knew good times. It's gonna run
I know how to do
I was on Sandman's, I bet like Bita was there.
I was there, we're about to like have this mud wrestling match.
Oh, I got clapped in like 10 seconds.
And it's like, and then he's like, oh, let's play Big Troll again.
And I missed all this.
It was just terrible.
But Sam, but um, but RG you're not a bad guy. You're you're actually not a good you know, you always says about me
You always said I like site you like you always
You you don't like me you always I didn't say that I don't like Jimmy. That's the person I don't like
I had Jimmy on my show once he showed me his breasts. I did it. He really wanted to see his big fat man tits
I didn't want to see them, but I know you didn't he forces tits on your show. I remember
And then I went on his show one time, and then he showed me his tits there.
And then all of a sudden, I'm getting like, you know, people are straight.
When he sees you he wants to show you his mantis is very weird. He claims to be straight
I don't think he is I think he's I think I didn't say he was gay and like him and Sam
He's gay 100% gay. Yeah, I think I think maybe he is but yeah
I mean, it's just it's a little bit and then I was like then KZ comes on with beta, right?
And he's like, oh beta you asked me to like come on the show and then she's like
Read the text message and then it says go on beat his show
And I was like well I was like well that says that sounds like somebody else in the text message
Who sent it and be told me to shut the fuck up and so that's what I left her show
Yeah, I just I was just waking up during all that so I don't know I didn't get to play with the casey
No, which I always appreciate
Pics is bugging me. I got a lot about be good. No one second one second one second one second. I'll show you I
Just wanted to show you the video. I found his modeling his modeling photo his video even see this
Yeah, here you are G. Ah, that's funny. It's good
Goodbye, there it is good stuff. He has too many teeth though. One two
41 homeless. Yeah. Oh, I see. All right. Thank you. Thank you. I love you. Okay
See, yeah, there we go
32 inch hat. How's everyone doing? We're having a nice time
Yeah
Guys, did somebody send me a cash app for the shaving?
I mean, I said, I said, did you have an eyebrow
for like $200?
I'll do my whole head for $250?
Cash app?
I mean, I'll do it on stream.
I'll go right now, get a lady big.
I'll do it with a razor.
And but I have to also use electric a little bit didn't want to do that
I'll put my cash up in the in the chat or whatever you guys can also come like like a if everybody like gave $5
five times thirty three six nine ten oh fifteen if I got 150 I
Would do that. I would probably do the head tonight because I'm drunk enough, but I'm gonna get some weed and
Wake up with a shaved head tomorrow, but I don't think I looked at that with a shaved head
You see what I would look like I
You guys want to see that I mean, it's like
Save my bush. I can't show my bush really. I mean I could show it
I'll do it for for $200
But all you'll be able to see is the hair and a bunch of shaving cream and my finished product with not my wiener showing
Just the top
Anybody interested? I'll tell I'll type in my cash up guys. You can you can all work together
You can guys conspire figure it out
I need to do another
Message hey, let's do this. Yeah, let's I'll be right back. What's wrong with peer reading?
Bernie, I'll do the peer readings. I do need so many sends a hundred dollars. I'll spend 75 of that
Walk down the city howl tomorrow
And I will get my permit and then I'll do peer reeks
Remember when I pulled my okay. Yes. So one night on my show
Bita dropped her phone and then she
Decided to change her underwear with the phone on the floor. I remember that I
Remember that all I saw was it looked like it looked like
Ever see Cinderella or no sleeping beauty when they all the all the thorny things
Happened when all these thorns grew on the castle. That was like Vita's bush
Run the clip. I can't show it. I mean it was not probably a poor monk. It was so dark and hairy and stuff
but
I mean, it's somewhere in my archives is somewhere in my archives actually guys
I do want to show you I want to show you the how on the cold codex is coming along
sleepy's like you made that with AI. Well, yeah, bitch because I can't take two thousand transcripts and then
Myself imagine me taking two thousand transcripts and I'm going through every finding every single name and every topic on the show
Thank God for AI. It just makes my life easier, but I did say go through all my transcripts and find every name and
And go, I mean, so it's like basically I'm like the more of the boss and she doesn't she doesn't get AI
She doesn't get it even though she uses it on my pictures and shit
What a dumb fucktard really like an AI version of the clip. That's a good idea
That's a good idea
I can do it
I'm about to make a bakelips one because bakelips made really insulting shit about me
Here i'm gonna do a little clip and just take a little breather real quick
Hopefully you guys will stay I
Swear is better than Kodak black with salmon whatever salmon playing some Kodak black song
It sounded like just like it sounded like some some mentally disabled person yelling words and then I have thoughtful
Like I actually put work into my AI AI shit, right? I actually like
We'll write the songs. I'll
Figure out the art and all the kind of stuff and then animate all the art and put it all
I mean it takes me maybe maybe the couple of
I mean it doesn't it's not like hours and hours of work, but it's like a couple hours at least and
Then is it I'll use AI. Well, it's like I work with the AI. It's kind of like
But is she gonna be so dumb you don't get it. It's okay. See it. They are dumb
You know, they are really dumb, but let me just like I'm just gonna put a short little
So I can go pee and just take a deep little breather and stuff
There's no one on panel right now
but um
Just give me a minute, and I promise it's better than Sandman plays is like has more
Things to look at interesting. He doesn't even all he shows is his his stupid fake app
Which is at AI by the way his avatar photo, but even my avatar photos. It's like it's more realistic than whatever he whatever shit
He's doing right
Okay, I'm gonna play this sermon electric profit. This is like a good one. This is a good one
Yeah, I think you're like I think you like this one. Just just give me a chance. Yeah guys
Just give it a chance
If you don't like it then fuck fuck me never I'll never like watch my videos again. If this is okay
Okay, it's okay, and maybe I'm not such a loser. Okay, I put a lot of work into this
Okay, here we go. Enjoy this over back. I did pee and stuff
Ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh
I'm your disco prophet, king of the dance floor craze
Leading you wild and crazy through the neon haze
Laughing loud, spinning around, I'm your close delight
Come join the party, we're wild all night
get your worries leave your cares join the tribe with me on flares echoes of funky bass and beat
out while sermon can't be beat step by step let's break the mold in this laughter be bold madness enjoy
Yeah, what's up, man? What's up? I mean he complains about Ziggy said something terrible to me
Did you do something terrible to somebody? Yeah, no, I got to sit here by my little buddy
Bader that they see smart. Where is Peter? Where is that sexy ass?
I want to think he's smart and he was like I was like somebody does something cold and he sent me here
Okay, what you well, he sent you to the right place. Hey, say hello. How are you doing? I'm doing good. I miss you
I
I've been okay, I've been okay, you know, it's like this one thing after another
I'm basically dealing with like people that are a little bit mental and I don't know
I'm a little bit mental sometimes but like beta I'm trying to give her advice and say
Oh God beta Jesus Christ. She's mental with shit. Yeah. Oh, by the way, we're at war with Iran and uh, yeah
She's from Iran, right? I mean it's like I was like I was like I was like, okay
You know I'm being porn bombed by 300 glow with like not porn bomb
But he's putting like you know putting a gun in his mouth on my stream and she's like shut the fuck up
Well, I can't even get the water and I'm like I'm trying to help you lady
Like and so I'll just leave I don't just left and then it's like, yeah
People like what I have when I have a smoke with I'm entertaining it, right? I don't know. They don't get it
Don't get it. What do you mean? You're entertaining is that what you said?
Well, what I when I'm kind of fighting with them and I you know, you heard me
I said the n-word the other night
Sucks to entertain with fighting, but yeah, that's what that's in the n-word on our show to Sam and stuff
And everyone was just laughing and like I'll say man sauce dude. I hate right
He does suck. Oh, yeah, I'm kissing my cat
You love me
So how is how's your girlfriend? Oh?
She's doing fine. We're we're still raising chickens and stuff like that
Chickens with his girlfriend guys guys. It's like it's like Green Acres
It's called Ziggy's a I
Love it. Oh
Wow, you we were kind of wanting to know
like summer I miss you summer wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry
Yes, you're managing back you got it
Guess what? Oh, no, I want a man. I want my management. Yeah, you have a standard mod
You can get a stick standard mod. Uh, I don't really get a standard mod. Actually, do you know what a standard mod is?
Like what it's not good. It's not nothing dude. It's like hold on. I need to make somebody else a manager
Yeah, I got another manager. I got another manager coming in the crew. Yeah, there we go
Very good. It's not like I'm coming up here asking for it, dude.
Hey,
Hey, are you good? Did I do good? I think I just did something good. I think I just did something good and burning joint
I'll make you a standard with burning joint if somebody comes in asking for reading next time. Can you say go to dude?
Go to psyche go to psyche at psyche at cult of psyche calm. Don't say it costs $9,000. Can you do this one fucking thing for me?
What did you make it?
Nope, there's this guy that watches you Bader you know who Bader. Yeah, I know Bader's
Can you give him a fucking reading for once? Yeah, is he here? What's his name? He's he's watching Bader
He's watching watching Bader. Yeah, Bader speak now or her furrow. I'm not gonna do it unless Bader says it's Bader in the chat
He's here. He's fucking here. He's the one that sent me here. He's the one that sent me here
Guys you want to see what I see on Instagram every day and what makes me happy and live
About Vader look at this
Wait about Vader. No, not about Vader, but about these guys. It's thing that isn't his twin brother
We don't know what you're doing see that right there. Yeah, I'm not oh my god. He's still here. I think that is left. Look at this guy
That's a
I love Zea. I was on Zea's show the other night and I said I wanted to lick his
butthole and he told me he asked me to do how I do it and I demonstrated and he
said it's a possibility. Oh god. Why oh god? I just I'm not like that. You don't
like pepsin Zea? Yeah I don't.
I don't really care.
Man.
Okay.
Do what you do, man.
I don't give a fuck.
I'm going to do what I do.
I don't judge you.
I don't.
And everybody else does.
And I don't.
Yeah.
I was on Zayas the other night with Pebs.
I did Zayas reading.
Is he booty goon?
Is that Vader?
Summer come up and say hi somewhere. I miss you
I want to find out about the king's protest and the no kings protests and stuff and
I know I have problems with like Christine and stuff, but I you know and
He had me gotta give me a phone number last night. He's like call this number. It was in Virginia
No, I mean the phone a man to pick up the phone
Booty Ziggy says yeah, they said I could lick his ass. He did he did
You know, he said it would be okay
He didn't like it was an invitation. I said I wanted to have a threesome with pebs in Zaya
I did and they both said maybe oh
Shit
From working in a shower, okay, maybe someone will come on and say hi that cuz we I've been missing summer
I've been missing summer. I haven't seen her in a while. I was kind of worried and stuff, you know
I'm having problems with some people and stuff well wait wait I maybe I'm like speaking too much like I don't know what
Pebs looks like
Okay, it's okay in the beginning out. What a fuck paps. Yeah, I called a man because Goddy
I said I said I said I said I want to do a prank call tonight and Goddy's like I have a number for you
Give me a number
I called the number they didn't pick up the first time the second time they picked up
I heard a man talking like complaining and I heard Amanda's voice and I was like are you sleeping with?
Hey, did you sleep with my boyfriend lady and Goddy called me to call and then I think it was Amanda. I
Know I know you have it somewhere. I'm sorry. I don't want to get you for I know you
Was funny it was funny
I had to believe that he said the whole whole month it was God that it gave the number yeah
It got he gave a whole number out on my show. I called it like I like I don't know who this is
He's like oh, it's a nice person and stuff and then it was like
it was down like a couple arguing and kind of bet and bed and stuff like that and
But then I kind of recognize the man's voice and he's like it was Amanda
I was like oh shit and Amanda was already on this over earlier. It was fun. It was funny
It was funny, so so do you ever bring up like, you know good-looking girls up here?
Of course, I do. I had Crystal Marie and Jamie on last night. Oh
my new crystal Marie
How that shit
No, I good, you don't like that
Oh, she flies the air. She's a fucking airplay. She's a NASA. Oh, okay. She's a pilot, too
Dude, come on. Do you see a thing that isn't his brother? This thing that isn't his brother right there
What about girls? I mean on girls. I don't like girls. I mean, I'd like I mean, I like, you know, I
Like these guys right here. Oh my god, his butt. Oh
There they go. Yeah, I don't think she's mad. I mean she came up a couple times
Because what is this going on? What is going on here?
Look at this this one
Boy, I'm gonna start it over because look at what happens at first. Oh, no, what did you do? I
Don't know never mind
Man you're activist fuck
She wasn't mad. She actually was on the stream several times last night and you know, she she wasn't mad
I don't think that was before the prank call. I didn't know was her by the way
I didn't know crystal. No, I'm talking about Amanda. Oh
Yeah
That was naughty
I'm sorry. Hey guys, look at this one. This is good
It just says someone give me the thumbs up. What you were think what was in your minds guys?
What was
Do you have like
Like manette
Yeah, I don't know what's going on here. Oh, it's a thumbs up. Look look he's a cutie
Manette is cutie now. Oh
Look at this
I'm not looking like that. No, it's just somebody give me a thumbs up
It's literally strong one of this.
It's literally this.
What?
Yeah, what?
Is this a thumbs up?
dude bro the cool thing man too like I'm a tattoo guy too and I didn't know you
had a bunch of tattoos on your arms that's pretty cool you know I have tattoos all over
yeah I do oh yeah I have I have everything over my own you see this one
Ziggy look at the back what is that see her yeah what is that it's a succubus
Suckibus. Oh, you already knew.
That's how it's it is avatar. Well, actually, okay, so there's a tattoo artist. I'm Freddie Negretti
He's pretty famous tattoo artist. He's a Mexican prison black and white artist
He did the black and white and I had to put in building blue and purple hair by like a northern California artist
Yeah, nice nice
Your tattoo artist. Can you give me a tattoo?
Give you a tattoo. Yeah, we said I'll pay for it. Yeah, okay
And then we can kiss afterward. We kiss
I'm not kissing. No, man. What are you talking about? Just man. I'll wear my wig. I'll get the blonde wig again
Nope, you'll never know the difference. It's vegan page. I don't work that way man. I love women
But you won't know it's just a kiss and then I'll be full. I'll be fully in the female outfit. Come on, dude
You know, where is it verse Vader by the way?
I think he's afraid
although he isn't isn't he my sexual
oh we have a guest on tonight let's welcome our guest
okay
God, do we had some fun? I didn't mean wasn't that fun when you called Amanda's house?
He got it
He's oh, he just left. Oh my god. Yeah, we called Amanda's house. It was so funny though
I deleted the stream, but I was like I heard like
Typical that's actually a typical guy man. I love that guy
Yeah, he's laughed and then he leaves. I mean he's on usually for like five seconds. Well, that's what we used to do
You know fuck with people just by laughing on there. Oh, yeah, we came from IPT man, like
Just like me, I'm not an IPT either but it's like
Wouldn't we better on ip2 than like, you know, some of the people that are on there
I don't get it. I don't get why and then people are making fun
Oh, he wanted to be an ip2 and he can never be on it
It's like I really don't care anymore than I know it's a suicid network
And doesn't matter that doesn't matter if you were there you're part of it, right? Yeah, I'm part of it
I think I'm really a part of it
I do and he's my daddy
I wasn't a streamer or anything with a beat it should be on personally. I think beta is like would qualify
I don't know like there's people with like three actually three live
No, you would qualify
Yeah, no, you would
Bunny's and shit, I think I mean it's like I think there's a bunch of people could qualify
But it's like they just picked the wrong people and stuff, right?
What what what my point is is that like why don't you why don't you register yourself for IP to and then?
Flight a few times, but she didn't came up or do I wrote well I do I mean I'm cammed up
I literally have thousands of hours of footage.
I'm literally like crashing on half of the time.
I literally was born by Joker and Benny.
And, you know, I understand why.
Yeah, but my other point is,
is there's a bunch of dudes that are IP2
that fucking like came from that.
You know what I mean, like even in the chat, even in the fucking going up on live with
them, whatever, and that was one of them.
Who is this person?
Is CB like the woman that showed me her milk bags that night, and she has these big milk
bags?
I don't know who you're talking about.
Who?
Remember, who's that lady?
Who's that woman?
I know it's not what it used to be.
There's a woman.
CB, yeah.
She's cool.
it was like, what?
Is she trying to come up?
No, not right now, but she was like,
it was like basically like a Roseanne bar
except like 300 pounds heavier.
And she had these huge disgusting,
like wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait,
can I put it in your perspective?
Yes.
Like basically her back hurts.
No, she was going like this
Yeah, she's okay, it is the same for
He said I was like section harassing her on tiktok. I was she's actually resting me on
Stop
See, right? No, I'm telling her right now. CB. Would I tell you about getting on these dudes about crazy shit?
Stop it right now. I don't like it. Is that people?
She's not gonna do it. She's not going out, but people believe, you know, a woman saying this stuff
I'm not mad about it, but it's like a little bit offensive because look CB
You're gonna be fucking blocked out of my fucking bullshit
If you fucking act like this, don't do that.
Have you ever heard of the Me Too movement, where it's like,
we're making an accusation and then everyone starts like hating the man?
That's what it's kind of like.
Oh no, right?
Yeah.
It's always like that.
It's stupid.
And my woman Jan loves me, but then I have a problem with this one guy, right?
Bader Bader Bader Bader was Bader he love he loves Jan and CB and I'm like I
Like I like I like chicken cakes justice for me. There's chicken cakes chicken cakes is fucking
What jazz
Army's different than chicken cakes
Mmm. I love I love chicken cakes. I know because you love chicken. You're like the chicken fucker from South Park, right?
No, I love how she talks. Okay. Okay. I'm sorry. That would maybe too much. Yeah
And then but we have fucking Vader that's like, oh no, we gotta get rid of
You know, he's telling me in a group. Hey, so so so she's saying we're gonna threesome with me and you
Would you ever do that?
No, that's not what I'm saying. Hold on. What'd you do that if she was there and I was
In a minute and then you can ask that question
So
with my woman and CB and then little Vader,
he gets all jealous and stuff.
He gets jealous.
Oh, Vader, come on.
Oh, yeah.
It's like-
Remember when I got naked for Vader on his stream?
I was in like, basically a thong on his stream.
Right, yeah.
And then like, so I-
He loved it.
I think he does actually we did. I remember he was like you they got the best dream of his
He said it was the best time in his life when I was like I didn't man. I didn't even look you did it
It's like I saw I saw the song you're picking at my song
You must have seen it
it's like Sam and like
I was more laughing about him being like hey, show it show it like I'm like
We dare me to show it
Yeah, and then JT was there and he was like don't do that. Don't don't oh JT says it's such a party pooper
No, he was saying that to Bader. I know but he was trying to poop the party because Bader was having a good time
Then she's like, oh stop. You know stop. I wasn't like I never looked at all dude
Anyone wants to talk to Ziggy myself. I'm gonna get an NPM. I'm gonna go get some more alcohol
I guess but anyone's gonna get more what kind of alcohol I get these harder lemonade actually
I think we'll be voodoo Rangers and stuff
What I don't know what the fuck that is a voodoo ranger is a I guess they're like, you know, there are these ranger voodoo ranger
voodoo ranger
Yeah, they're basically these beers that are like, you know, basically they say
Adobo Dumballa, give me the power I beg of you and then you turn into a check you go
Get down down. I want to get down with you, baby
No, don't call me a baby. Don't call me baby because another baby
You know why you know why cuz I someone send me a picture of you. You look like the guy from Good Charlotte, you know with a cuter butt
I fucking hate you right now because you do look like that, right? I
Wasn't I saw the emo haircut. I saw you. It was you it was you with an emo haircut
You have tattoos on your eyes. Hey, you and you know what it is. It was you. It was you
It was not were you the lead singer for good Charlotte?
No guitar and why was the pause for?
guitarist you play the guitarist for good show I knew I knew it
I knew you were involved with the car
Never did anything after you know what good charlotte's about it's about a spider named charlotte. Oh, yeah a web
It was it's about good. You know why because she saved the pigs life
You know Charlotte with the spider the best heart of any animal on the farm
And, and, you know, don't be mean to, you know, Vader all the time, you know, all that kind of shit.
That's funny that you recognize the Good Charlotte thing.
Hey, I recognize Good Charlotte.
I recognize it. Hey, but you don't like a guy to lick your butt?
No, no, no way ever what if what if what if you're having says the woman and then you just feel something back there
Are you gonna look back? No, I love I love thick women. That's what I know. I know you do
I know you do but whatever he just felt something back there. Would you like kick me out of the bed?
He wouldn't he said no he said no
He's but no no
He said he wouldn't kick me out of the bed if he felt something back there. He would just continue going with the thick women
Okay, right, right you're getting kicked the fuck out
Now I'm getting kicked out of bed now. I'm getting kicked out, but before you were just paying attention to the tits
right
By the way, I like I'm gonna emo you aren't emo guys bisexual though. You didn't like the song. This is what you're saying. I
Love the songs and I love you
Thank you
You're very welcome
You're really cute. And so do you have a girlfriend? You have a girlfriend?
Absolutely. Yeah, I have CB and I have Jan now CB and Jan
I mean, this is not like, you know, the Beverly Hillbillies. Okay. Oh, no, no, it's not Beverly Hillbillies
No, you know what CB and Jan look like they're both over 300 pounds
Well, you want to be crushed to death
Mm-hmm, and with this with a skinny with a skinny guy tasting your butthole. How about that?
One time just one time. Don't even look back. Just just go with it. Just go with it
You're gonna crush you to death. I'm gonna pull you out. I'm gonna pull you from under there
I'm the one that's gonna pull you from under there. I just can't believe that you pulled me out of like what I've done
I'm sorry fucking Loki. I'm sorry. I'm super attractive. That's fucking
Pretty impressive that you pulled me out of something. I've done it too much. Okay. I'll turn back. I'll turn up a little bit
I'm gonna turn you on. I'm gonna turn you on watch while I turn you on one second. I'm gonna turn you on a little bit
The better what are you talking?
I don't know. I don't what are you talking about? Nothing. Just ignore me. Okay. I'm talking about your looks
You're not the one that's gay. I I know you're not but you have humongous milk bags
I mean I could like basically
It started there. Okay
Who are you talking to right now? CB? Oh?
CB. Yeah. Oh, yeah, she totally has like
I'm in a three diamond and CB
I'm gonna put these like milk extractors and I'm gonna start a dairy and then everyone will die because the milk will make you
Everybody would die
Everybody that's crazy that you called me out. That's fucked up
Good Charlotte. It's okay. I like I like your music. Don't say that again. It was a good year
You had a good run. You had a good run. I did I did other things too though. I've done
You ever take a shower with a bunch of guys I
Was in the military, yeah
My I rest my case. I took a shower with the guys too, but I was in jail with Mexicans
Yeah
I mean I can't believe you called me out you little asshole dude like I kind of want to get off the phone now
I'm sorry. Hey Ziggy. I love you though. If you want to go you can go but hey you come back any time and Ziggy
I want to cuddle you to death one night.
No, shut up.
And come on, don't do that.
I'm going to pull you off from under CB and Kate's chicken
army, and then I'm going to kiss you like the prince
and bring you back to life.
How about that?
Oh, my god.
Honestly, I don't think that band would ever really.
I know
AFI right and tell me about the AFI
AFI we talk about no, I know every diggy. I know everything. I've been someone told me I never got in the
Yes, you're a drummer for them for a short period of time. No, I didn't know I was
No, no, I ended up being in like the I did helped out helped
help. You helped out with AFI? No, with a double driver and stuff like that.
Marilyn Manson? No, no, I wish. Fuck. Hey, you know, I know Marilyn Manson's friend,
Jessica. Have you heard of Jackoff Jill? Uh, no, but I've heard of Jackoff Jill.
Look at my cat Jackoff Jill. I'm friends with her.
the
house of the gas
No, oh, I don't know any a lot relying because I could tell what live from a million miles away. You said no
I'm saying I don't know any of them. Yeah, yeah, don't okay. I'll see you at the next goth festival, okay?
Hey, hey
You have a sweet white ass, that's all I have to say
Are you saying are you saying that because I'm gothic
Can you have a sweet white ass? It's really
Mine I like you like
Yeah, you like you like pal
I like pale men. I like pale men I do. Especially with like the hair cut with like the black
hair with like it's the comb in like three different directions and they play guitar
for like.
Well I'm just saying that we dye it though.
I know you do. I know that no way that hair is not just black it's like a black purple
kind of color.
Yeah.
You know the bottles of Lady Claire all right and you put like three of those in your hair
I know I know I know guys. No, I was I was never like just to clarify
I was never in like Marilyn Manson. You're in good. Charlotte. You're you're the guitars for good Charlotte. You were
I'm not saying that stuff, but um, I know hey, I'm psychic I did I did have a band though
I wish that you guys would like appreciate
Tell us the channel
I did have a band that was called that said
And I loved it. I loved it the most so you know
I know. Oh, I got it. I got it. I got it. I have a text message. I got to go. I have a text message from somebody
I need the answer. I'm gonna play a quick video and stuff, but thank you for being on the show.
Good for you, man.
Ziggy, oh, you can stay here if you want. I just had to break you.
Oh, no, I'm gonna take off, man.
Okay, thank you. Thank you for having me up, though.
Ziggy, Ziggy, Ziggy, I'm gonna lick you from the top to the bottom.
Okay. Oh, no. Oh, can you do the song though? Can you do the, I want to lick, lick, lick you from your head to your throat.
I mean, all I can do is sing it.
I can't play the original Algae Copyright Show, but I can make up my own.
I wanna lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick
I want to lick-lick-lick-lick-lick from his friend, Ziggy.
Were you expecting me already, so can you please do that?
Ziggy, you bent over, and ZB, you're on top of ZB, and Jan's chicken army.
I'm going to lick your butt, and then...
You're gonna just be happy about it. All right. Hey, I'm gonna take off man
Hey, yeah, I need you to stop talking about that, please and I won't never stop talking about it
I have a great night though. Bye. No, no, I'm serious. Yeah. No, no, I won't you know, I'll see you in court
I'll see you in court. I'll see you in court
I'm not taking anybody out of here get the fuck out of here
Love you Ziggy. Thank you for being on the show. That was fun. That was fun. No, I didn't I didn't need to talk to my friend real quick
I'll play moon in the skull cup
Here you go guys enjoy the song this is called moon in the skull cup
Ziggy you do a sweet ass. I'm sorry. I
Love you. I love you. I love you
He didn't know he's still on I love this guy. So sexy. Hey guys look up good charlotte
Look at the guitarist
Isn't no more he's still on oh he left okay, okay, I'll be right back guys
Enjoy the moon in the skull cup. Enjoy this one. We're back. I'll be right back
Hush beyond the temple Light where the lilies drink the dark
You will rise with a crescent in your hair And a forest in your heart
Paragrene whisper on your hand Red silk moving like flame
You sing the hidden names of things and nothing stays the same
Low to side in the midnight grove, Jasmine breathing at your feet
Everyone begins to listen when your wild song turns sweet
Take a throne from what we fear and beauty out of all
Soft as nectar on the tongue
Sharp as iron through a lie
You are mercy with a knife of truth
You are moon fire in the sky
Crazy dark river, a wisdom moon upon your face.
Sing me tender, sing me fierce.
Split the veil and calm the sea.
Holy outcast, royal storm, make a fear.
Syllables that frighten mouths won't hold
You bless the unclean, lift the cast off
Crown the margins with your heart
And every buried exile truth comes
Beating through the heart
Make a sunrise from the tomb, sweet voice, cool
Split the veil and call the sea
Holy outcast, royal storm
Make a fearless song of me
When they call me strange
Let me be strange with you
Does not fright